[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many songs are there on the original Black Dog soundtrack?", "correct_answer": "11", "incorrect_answers": ["12", "10", "13"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This North American river is also called Kaniatarowanenneh, which means big waterway in Mohawk.", "correct_answer": "Saint Lawrence River", "incorrect_answers": ["Rio Grande", "Colorado", "Ohio River"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these names refers to a large group of asteroids in Jupiters orbit?", "correct_answer": "The Trojan asteroids", "incorrect_answers": ["The Hellenic asteroids", "The Roman asteroids", "The Martian asteroids"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1994 movie starred Tommy Lee Jones, Robert Downey Jr. and Juliette Lewis.", "correct_answer": "Natural Born Killers", "incorrect_answers": ["Cape Fear", "The Fugitive", "Gun Crazy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do you add to steel to make it stainless?", "correct_answer": "Chromium", "incorrect_answers": ["Copper", "Zinc", "Bronze"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What nations gas group, PEMEX, made headlines in 1974?", "correct_answer": "Mexico", "incorrect_answers": ["United Arab Emirates", "Venezuela", "Panama"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the Filipino word salita mean in English?", "correct_answer": "word", "incorrect_answers": ["phrase", "sentence", "meaning"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Philippines has the worlds largest deposit of heavy water which can be used for atomic energy, in spectroscopy, and as an automobile fuel. What makes heavy water different from water?", "correct_answer": "The presence of deuterium", "incorrect_answers": ["An extra hydrogen molecule", "One  less hydrogen molecule making it HO not H2O", "An extra oxygen molecule"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Guess the missing number from the following sequence: 12, 24, 48, ___, 120, 240, 264?", "correct_answer": "96", "incorrect_answers": ["80", "60", "72"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Art Paul Schlosser wrote a song about peanut butter called Have A Peanut Butter Sandwich.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What virus, causing worldwide sterility, does Blofeld threaten to spread, in the movie On Her Majestys Secret Service?", "correct_answer": "Omega", "incorrect_answers": ["Teta", "Zeta", "Epsilon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If compared to a camera, what part of the human eye is its aperture?", "correct_answer": "Pupil", "incorrect_answers": ["Iris", "The cones", "Optic nerve"]}]